RG 079:001, Department of Environmental Protection: Central Office
Connecticut State Library
- Series 1. Commissioner, 1957-2004
  - Legislation Files, 1971-1991
    - 1993-140
      - Records, 1989-1991
        - DEP Package, 1989 (Box 2)
        - Agency Comments-Legislation (Box 2)
        - Miscellaneous, 1989 (Box 2)
        - Water Discharge Permit Regulations (Box 2)
        - Flood Management Regulations (Box 2)
        - Microencapsulated Methyl Parathion Regulations (Box 2)
        - Nuisance Wildlife Regulations (Box 2)
        - Potable Water Grant Regulations (Box 2)
        - Privately Stocked Waters (Box 2)
        - Mandatory Reporting of Spills (Box 2)
        - Road Salt Regulations (Box 2)
        - Recreation Law Enforcement (Box 2)
        - Soil and Water Conservation District Regulations (Box 2)
        - Solid Waste Plan (Box 2)
        - Status Report Regulations (Box 2)
        - Striped Bass Regulations (Box 2)
        - Underground Storage Tanks Regulations (Box 2)
        - Water Compliance-General Conditions and Procedure Regulations (Box 2)
        - X-Ray Regulations (Box 2)
        - Press (Box 2)
        - Petroleum Settlement Funds (Box 3)
        - Indian Affairs/Forest Fire Appropriation-Public Hearing (Box 3)
        - AAC Motorboats on Bolton Pond and Gardner Lake (Box 3)
        - AAC on Appropriation for Project Oceanology (Box 3)
        - AAC Collection facilities for Used Crankcase Motor oil (Box 3)
        - Staff-Miscellaneous (Box 3)
        - Hazardous Waste/SARA Title II-Public Hearing (Box 3)
        - Environmental Fees/Environmental Protection Fund/Bottle Bill-Pubic Hearing (Box 3)
        - Wildlife Bureau-Reports (Box 3)
        - Grass Carp (Box 3)
        - Environment Magazine (DEP) (Box 3)
        - E-2000 Advisory Board (Box 3)
        - Air Permit Regulations (Box 3)
        - Auto Emission Standards-NESCAUM (Box 3)
        - New England Governors (Box 3)
        - Miscellaneous-Newsletters (Box 3)
        - Governor’s OC Reports/CONEG (Box 3)
        - CT Delegation-Bills (Box 3)
        - Legislative Priorities, 1990 (Box 3)
        - Clean Air Act-Summaries/Comments (Box 3)
        - Permits/Licenses/Fees (Box 3)
        - DEP Budget (Box 3)
        - Benzene Emission Standard (Box 3)
        - Clean Air-General (Box 3)
        - Senate Energy Committee-Use of Methane (Box 3)
        - New England Energy Caucus-Clean Air Act (Box 3)
        - House Public Works-Clean Air and Highways (Box 3)
        - BALF Corp. (Box 3)
        - Route 6-Wetlands (Box 3)
        - Groton Sewer Outfall (Box 3)
        - Truck Weight Station (Greenwich) (Box 3)
        - MA Landfills-Webster/Couglar (Box 3)
        - TYCO-Water Diversion Application (Box 3)
        - McKinney Wildlife Refuge (Box 3)
        - Silver Lands (Box 3)
        - Shakespeare Theater (Box 3)
        - Marketing-Recycling/Economic Development (Box 4)
        - Packaging (Box 4)
        - NGA Taskforce-Waste Management (Box 4)
        - CONEG-Source Reduction Task Force (Box 4)
        - Solid Waste-Ash Siting (1988 Bill, OLR Memo and Wisconsin Law) (Box 4)
        - Demolition Waste (Box 4)
        - Recycling Update, 1989 September (Box 4)
        - Mute Swans Regulations (Box 4)
        - Water Diversion Regulations (Box 4)
        - Freedom of Information (Box 4)
        - Regulations-Notice from Secretary of State (Box 4)
        - Feasibility of a Diesel Inspection and Maintenance Program for CT (Box 4)
        - Governor (Box 4)
        - DEP EQ Programs (Box 4)
        - State Superfund, 1987 (Box 4)
        - LIS (Box 4)
        - Low level Radiation Waste (Box 4)
        - CONEG (Box 4)
        - NGA (Box 4)
        - Quinnipiac River (Box 5)
        - Task Force-Aquifer Protection (Box 5)
        - Toxic Air Regulations (Box 5)
        - Task Force Bulky Waste Disposal (Box 5)
        - Task Force Septic System (Box 5)
        - Task Force Water Company Lands (Box 5)
        - Dam Safety Regulations (Box 5)
        - Regulations-Directives on Procedures (Box 5)
        - Environmental Quality Fees (Box 5)
        - Asbestos (Box 5)
        - Acid Rain (Box 5)
        - New England Governors and Eastern Canadian Premiers Conference (Box 5)
        - Air (Box 5)
        - Amerbelle (Box 5)
        - Appalachian Trail (Box 5)
        - Boating Fund, Fisheries, and Hunting Fees (Box 5)
        - Bottle Bill (Box 5)
        - Cannata-Connecticut River (Box 5)
        - Coastal Management Act-Adjudications (Box 5)
        - Coastal Management (Box 5)
        - Connecticut Hazardous Waste Management (Box 5)
        - Connecticut Plan of C&D-Revisions (Box 5)
        - Connecticut Environment Roundtable (Box 5)
        - Composting (Box 5)
        - Contaminated Fish (Box 5)
        - Larson’s Connecticut River Preserve District (Box 5)
        - Crystal Water Company (Box 5)
        - Diesel Emissions (Box 5)
        - EPA-DEP Advisory Board (Box 5)
        - Global Warning (Box 5)
        - Governor’s Office (Box 5)
        - Economic Development Cabinet (Box 5)
        - KELP (Box 5)
        - Legislative Overview, 1989 (Box 5)
        - Conservation (Box 5)
        - Water (Box 6)
        - Related (Box 6)
        - Air (Box 6)
        - Limited Liability, HB 7096 (Box 6)
        - Waste (Box 6)
        - Stop and Shop/Finner Site (Box 6)
        - Oil Spill Legislation (Box 6)
        - Permits (Box 6)
        - Press Release (Box 6)
        - Recycling (Box 6)
        - Recycling Facility (Box 6)
        - DEP/GOV Speeches-Comments (Box 6)
        - U.S.T. Amendment (Box 6)
        - Governor Veto SB 148 (Box 6)
        - UST Clean up (Box 6)
        - Weir Farm (Box 6)
        - Silver Lake Project (Box 6)
        - DEP Legislative Testimony, 1991 (Box 6)
        - DEP Legislative Testimony, 1990 (Box 6)
        - DEP Legislative Testimony, 1989 (Box 6)
        - LIS License Plate (Box 6)
    - 2003-033 (part)
      - Records, 1971-1975
        - 1971-1975 (Box 1)
        - 1976 (Box 2)
        - 1977 (Box 3)
        - 1978-1979 (Box 4)
        - 1979-1980 (Box 5)
        - 1980-1981 (Box 6)
        - 1981-1983 (Box 7)
        - 1983 (Box 8)
        - 1984 (Box 9)
        - 1984 (Box 10)
        - Budget options, 1973-1989 (Box 10)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1973-1997
    - 1999-026
      - Connecticut Heritage Park System, 1989; 1 envelope (Box Shared box)
        Correspondence, legislation, brochure, consultant's report.
    - 1999-030
      - Records, 1991-1994; 1 folder (Box Shared box)
        Documents related to general ethics policy interpretations and boat launch facilities in Wethersfield.
    - 1999-035
      - Records, 1973-1994 (Box Shared box)
        Correspondence with Congressional members, Governor and the Attorney General's Office; speeches; press releases; transcripts of radio interviews; and other materials. Primary from Commissioners Pac, Carrothers, and Keeney.
    - 1999-173
      - Records, 1987-1997 (Box Box 1)
        - Dioxin regulation, 1987-1988 (Box Box 1)
        - Pfizer, Inc., 1989 (Box Box 1)
        - Timothy Keeney, 1991-1993 (Box Box 1)
        - Bi-weekly reports, 1991-1992 (Box Box 1)
        - Timothy Keeney, 1991, 1994 (Box 1)
        - Timothy Keeney press files, 1992-1993; 4 folders (Box Box 1)
        - Senior staff meeting handouts, 1992 (Box Box 1)
        - Long Island Sound study, 1992; 2 folders (Box Box 1)
        - Senior staff meeting notes, 1995, 1997 (Box Box 1)
- Series 6. Staff Services, 1972-1985; 1988-022
  - Director George Russell, 1971-1985
    - Acid Rain (Box 1)
    - Affirmative Action (Box 1)
    - Aerial Photography (Box 1)
    - Air Pollution (Box 1)
    - Air Quality (Box 1)
    - Army Corps of Engineers (Box 1)
    - ASPA (Box 1)
    - Auditors (Box 1)
    - Bicycling (Box 1)
    - Boating Safety (Box 1)
    - Connecticut Environmental Policy Act (CEPA) (Box 1)
    - CETA/WIN (Box 1)
    - Citizens’ Advisory Council (Box 1)
    - Citizens’ Bulletin (Box 1)
    - Civil Penalties Act (Box 1)
    - Civil Preparedness (Box 1)
    - Coastal Zone Management (Box 1)
    - Department of Commerce (Box 1)
    - Computer-Based Resource Units (Box 1)
    - Conferences (Box 2)
    - Connecticut Forest and Park Association (Box 2)
    - Connecticut River Gateway Commission (Box 2)
    - Conservation Commission (Box 2)
    - CRRA (Box 2)
    - Consultants (Box 2)
    - Council on Environmental Quality (Box 2)
    - Data Processing (Box 2)
    - Detergents and Phosphates (Box 2)
    - Dredging (Box 2)
    - Endangered Species (Box 2)
    - Environmental Education Report (Box 2)
    - EPA Citizen’s Bulletin (Box 2)
    - Energy (Box 2)
    - Environmental Education (Box 2)
    - Environment (Box 3)
    - Environmental Impact Statements (Box 3)
    - Environmental Review Team (Box 3)
    - Eutrophication (Box 3)
    - Farmington River Watershed Association (Box 3)
    - Flood Insurance (Box 3)
    - Flood Control (Box 3)
    - Forestry (Box 3)
    - Freedom of Information (Box 3)
    - Flood Plain Zoning (Box 3)
    - Garden Clubs (Box 3)
    - Hazardous Materials (Box 3)
    - Historical Commission (Box 3)
    - Housatonic Valley Association (Box 3)
    - Indian Affairs (Box 3)
    - Information and Education (Box 3)
    - Inland Wetlands (Box 3)
    - Institute of Public Services (Box 4)
    - Interagency Water Resources Planning Board (Box 4)
    - Lake Authorities (Box 4)
    - Columbia University Engineering Camp, Morris (Box 4)
    - Land Use (Box 4)
    - Library (Box 4)
    - Limited Liability (Box 4)
    - Litter Control (Box 4)
    - Litter Survey (Box 4)
    - Audubon Society (Box 4)
    - Connecticut Agriculture Experimental Stations Publications (Box 4)
    - Connecticut Conservation Association (Box 4)
    - Connecticut Wildlife Conservation Bulletin (Box 4)
    - Connecticut River Watershed Council (Box 4)
    - Conservation leader (Box 4)
    - Council of State Governments (Box 4)
    - Environmental Education (Box 4)
    - Milestone (Box 4)
    - National Wildlife Federation (Box 5)
    - Nature Conservancy News (Box 5)
    - New England River Basic Commission (Box 5)
    - Litter Control (Box 5)
    - Long Island Sound (Box 5)
    - Management Advisory Council (Box 5)
    - Manchester Community College (Box 5)
    - Marine Research (Box 5)
    - Minimum Stream Flow Standards (Box 5)
    - Mining and Mineral Extraction (Box 5)
    - Charles Mule (Box 5)
    - NASA Satellite Program (Box 5)
    - New Haven Rail Road (Box 5)
    - Natural Resources Council (Box 5)
    - Nature Centers (Box 5)
    - Natural Resources Center (Box 5)
    - Noise Pollution (Box 5)
    - Nuclear Energy (Box 5)
    - Ocean Pollution (Box 5)
    - Oil Pollution (Box 5)
    - Open Space (Box 6)
    - Open Space Program Project File (Box 6)
    - Organization Charts (Box 6)
    - OSHA (Box 6)
    - Outer Continental Shelf (Box 6)
    - Park Improvement EMP Projects (Box 6)
    - Park and Forest (Box 6)
    - Personnel (Box 6)
    - Permit Referral Information (Box 6)
    - Pesticide Control (Box 6)
    - Planning and Coordination (Box 6)
    - State Planning Council (Box 6)
    - Planning and Research (Box 6)
    - Press Release (Box 6)
    - Property Management (Box 6)
    - Property Review (Box 6)
    - Protected Plants (Box 6)
    - Public Hearings (Box 6)
    - Public Utilities Control Authority (Box 6)
    - Public Act 490 Court Cases (Box 6)
    - Publication-I and E (Box 6)
    - Purchasing (Box 6)
    - Radiation (Box 6)
    - Recycling (Box 6)
    - Regulation (Box 6)
    - Resource Conservation and Development Projects (Box 7)
    - Rivers (Box 7)
    - Rural Areas Development Committee (Box 7)
    - SCORP (Box 7)
    - Septic Systems (Box 7)
    - Small Watershed Programs (Box 7)
    - Snow Mobiles (Box 7)
    - Soil Conservation (Box 7)
    - Soil Erosion and Sedimentation (Box 7)
    - Solid Waste Control (Box 7)
    - Stream Encroachment Lines (Box 7)
    - Testimonial Dinners (Box 7)
    - Tidal Waters (Box 7)
    - Title X Program (BOR) (Box 7)
    - Trails (Box 7)
    - Transportation Control Plan (Box 7)
    - U.S. Dept. Environmental Protection/Dept. of Interior (Box 8)
    - Water Compliance (Box 8)
    - Water Compliance (208 Program) (Box 8)
    - Water Companies (Box 8)
    - Water Resource Plan (Title III) (Box 8)
    - Water Resource Planning (Box 8)
    - Water Resource Institute Advisory Committee (Box 8)
    - Water and Related Resources (Box 8)
    - Outdoor Recreation Action (Box 8)
    - Regional Planning Agency Newsletter (Box 8)
    - State Government Administration (Box 8)
    - Water in the News (Box 8)
    - White Memorial Foundation (Box 8)
    - Water Compliance (Box 8)
    - Cars (Box 9)
    - Central Office Managers Meeting (Box 9)
    - Commissioner’s Policy Letters (Box 9)
    - Connecticut Firsts (Box 9)
    - Conservation/Preservation (Box 9)
    - DEP Labor-Management Committee (Box 9)
    - Education Programs (Box 9)
    - Flex Time (Box 9)
    - General Letters (Box 9)
    - Inventories (Box 9)
    - Labor Relations (Box 9)
    - Land Acquisitions (Box 9)
    - Manager of the Year, 1984 (Box 9)
    - Management Development Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 9)
    - Parks and Historical Sites (Box 9)
    - Personnel (Box 9)
    - Personnel-General Letters (Box 9)
    - Planning and Coordination (Box 9)
    - Program Budget, 1984 (Box 9)
    - Ridgefield Water Supply Company (Box 9)
    - Rocky Neck State Park (Box 9)
    - Route 7 Linear Park (Box 9)
    - Rural Clean Water Program (Box 9)
    - Scantic River Park (Box 9)
    - Seagrant Program (Box 9)
    - SEE (Box 9)
    - Service Agreement/Correspondence (Box 9)
    - Shepaug Wild and Scenic River Estuary (Box 9)
    - Silver Sands-Milford (Box 9)
    - Space for DEP (Box 9)
    - Space (Box 9)
    - Trainee (Box 9)
    - Troutbrook (Box 9)
    - Urban Action Task Force (Box 9)
    - Waramaug Lake (Box 9)
    - Water Resources (Box 9)
    - West Rock Ridge State Park (Box 9)
    - Wildlife-Open Space Coordinator (Box 9)
    - Misc-George Russell (Box 9)
    - Statements, Special Letters, Testimonials, Articles, 1958-1966 (Box 10)
    - Statements, Testimonials, etc. (Box 10)
    - Statements, Testimonials, Messages, Progress Reports (Box 10)
    - George Russell (Box 10)
    - Hartford County Soil and Water Conservation District (Box 10)
    - Land Gift Booklet (Box 10)
    - Litchfield County Soil and Water Conservation District (Box 10)
    - Memoranda (Box 10)
    - Middlesex County Soil and Water Conservation District (Box 10)
    - Organizational Charts (Box 10)
    - PA 490 (Box 10)
    - Speech Material/Quotable Quotes (Box 10)
    - Speech Material (Box 10)
    - Water Resources (Box 10)
    - Water Resources Institute (Box 10)
    - Wetlands (Box 10)
    - Wild, Scenic, and Recreational River Systems (Box 10)
    - Windham County Soil and Water Conservation District (Box 10)
    - Annual Reports (Box Box 11)
    - ASPA Conference, 1983 April 16-19 (Box Box 11)
    - Bikeway, Windsor Locks Canal (Box Box 11)
    - The Bridge (Box Box 11)
    - Budget, 1981 (Box Box 11)
    - Candlewood Lake, 1978 (Box Box 11)
    - Connecticut Executive Management Program (Box Box 11)
    - Connecticut Environmental Protection Act (Box Box 11)
    - Connecticut River Diversion (Box Box 11)
    - Council on Environmental Quality (Box Box 11)
    - Dam Study (Box Box 11)
    - Dams (Box Box 11)
    - Executive Advisory Council (Box Box 11)
    - Fred Benedict (Box Box 11)
    - Goodyear Awards Program, 1984 (Box Box 11)
    - Housatonic River (Box Box 11)
    - Interstate Sanitation Commission (Box Box 11)
    - King’s Island, Windsor Locks (Box Box 11)
    - Land Gift Booklet Revision (Box Box 11)
    - Litter Control (Box Box 11)
    - Management Update (Box Box 11)
    - Manchester Community College (Box Box 11)
    - MAC-Quality of State Government (Box Box 11)
    - Norwalk River Project (Box Box 11)
    - Public Information Center (Box Box 11)
    - State Government and Administration (Box Box 11)
- Series 7. Bureau of Administration, 1967-1981; 1988-024 (part)
  - Assistant Commissioner Ralph Adkins Subject Files, 1967-1981
    - A-95 Review Information (Box 9-4)
    - Accomplishments (Box 9-4)
    - Account Numbers (Box 9-4)
    - Addressograph (Box 9-4)
    - Administrative-Confidential (Box 9-4)
    - Administrative Procedures Act (Box 9-4)
    - Administrative Regulations (Box 9-4)
    - Administrative Report to the Governor (Box 9-4)
    - Administrative Services Dept. (Box 9-4)
    - Advisory Council (Box 9-4)
    - Agency Mission Statement, 1979 (Box 9-4)
    - Air Compliance, after 1972 (Box 9-4)
    - Air Compliance Thru, 1972 December (Box 9-4)
    - Algae And Aquatic Weed Control (Box 9-4)
    - American Mgt. Assoc. (Box 9-4)
    - American Report, 1971-1972 (Box 9-4)
    - American Inst. of Planners (Box 9-4)
    - Appraisals (Box 9-4)
    - Air Regulations (Box 9-4)
    - Appropriations Act, 1974 (Box 9-4)
    - Appropriations Committee (Box 9-4)
    - ASPA (Box 9-4)
    - Assistant Attorney General (Box 9-4)
    - Atomic Energy Committee (Box 9-4)
    - Attendance Records (Box 9-4)
    - Attorney General-Correspondence (Box 9-4)
    - Audit-Agric. & Nat. Resources, 1967-1969 (Box 9-4)
    - Audit Report, 1971 October 1 - 1973 June 30 (Box 9-4)
    - Audit Report (Box 9-4)
    - Audit-Water Pollution Grants (Box 9-4)
    - Audubon Society, 1973 July 1 - 1976 June 30 (Box 9-4)
    - Automobiles, 1976 (Box 9-4)
    - Automobiles, 1975 (Box 9-4)
    - Automobiles, 1971-1974 (Box 9-4)
    - Banton Street (Box 9-4)
    - Basement Storage Area (Box 9-4)
    - Beach Erosion Projects (Box 9-4)
    - Beaches-Norwalk to Madison (Box 9-4)
    - Blaser, Zenit & Co. (Box 9-4)
    - Bluff Point (Box 9-4)
    - Boating Legislation (Box 9-5)
    - Boating Bill, 1973 (Box 9-5)
    - Boating, 1970-1972 (Box 9-5)
    - Boating, after 1972 (Box 9-5)
    - Boating Safety Fund (Box 9-5)
    - Bond Act, 1971 (Box 9-5)
    - Bond Commission Meeting, 1978 September 22 (Box 9-5)
    - Bond Commission Meeting, 1978 December 8 (Box 9-5)
    - Bond Commission Meeting, 1979 January 26 (Box 9-5)
    - Bond Commission Meeting, 1979 February 23 (Box 9-5)
    - Bond Commission Meeting, 1979 May 25 (Box 9-5)
    - Bond Commission Meeting, 1979 June 22 (Box 9-5)
    - Bond Commission Meeting, 1979 July 27 (Box 9-5)
    - Bond Commission Meeting, 1979 August (Box 9-5)
    - Bond Agenda Meeting, 1979 September (Box 9-5)
    - Bond Fund Meeting, 1979 October (Box 9-5)
    - Bond Commission, 1979 December (Box 9-5)
    - Bond Commission, 1980 January (Box 9-5)
    - Bond Commission, 1980 January (Box 9-5)
    - Bond Commission, 1980 June (Box 9-5)
    - Bond Commission, 1980 July (Box 9-5)
    - Bond Commission, 1981 January (Box 9-5)
    - Bond Commission, 1981 May (Box 9-5)
    - Bond Commission, 1981 August (Box 9-5)
    - Bond Commission, 1981 September (Box 9-5)
    - Bond Funds-Summary (Box 9-5)
    - Bond Fund-Summary- Alphabetical (Box 9-5)
    - Bond Fund Summary- Category (Box 9-5)
    - Bond Funds-Priority Projects (Box 9-5)
    - Bond Fund Status Report (Box 9-5)
    - Budget Div.-Correspondence, after 1974 (Box 9-5)
    - Budget Div.-Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box 9-5)
    - Budget, 1977-1978 (Box 9-5)
    - Bradford, Armory (Box 9-5)
    - Budge Position Priorities, 1977 (Box 9-5)
    - Brenneman, Russell L. (Box 9-5)
    - Burch, William R. (Box 9-5)
    - Bureau of Administration Minutes of Staff Meetings (Box 9-5)
    - Bureau of Outdoor Recreation (Box 9-5)
    - BOR, 1974-1975 (Box 9-5)
    - BOR, 1973 (Box 9-5)
    - Business Office (Box 9-9)
    - BOR, before 1973 (Box 9-9)
    - Bus Schedules (Box 9-9)
    - California Plan (Box 9-9)
    - Capital Budget, 1975-1976 (Box 9-9)
    - Capital Project Fund Request (Box 9-9)
    - Car Pool (Box 9-9)
    - Case Load of the Supreme Court-Report (Box 9-9)
    - Certification-Commissioner (Box 9-9)
    - CETA (Box 9-9)
    - Chart of General Funds Accounts (Box 9-9)
    - Citizen’s Committee to keep Connecticut Clean (Box 9-9)
    - Civil Defense (Box 9-9)
    - Civil Penalties (Box 9-9)
    - Claims Commission (Box 9-9)
    - Commission on Human Services (Box 9-9)
    - Commissioners Gill (Box 9-9)
    - Commissioners Memorandum #1 (Box 9-9)
    - Commissioners Correspondence-In (Box 9-9)
    - Community Development Action Plan (Box 9-9)
    - Commuter Bus Tickets (Box 9-9)
    - CETA Title 6 (Box 9-9)
    - CETA Title 1 (Box 9-9)
    - Comptrollers Meeting (Box 9-9)
    - Computer Services (Box 9-9)
    - Concessions (Box 9-9)
    - Conferences (Box 9-7)
    - Connecticut Action Now, Inc. (Box 9-7)
    - Connecticut Association of Assessing Officers (Box 9-7)
    - Connecticut Bank & Trust Co. (Box 9-7)
    - Connecticut Bus. & Ind. Assoc. (Box 9-7)
    - Connecticut Careers Trainees (Box 9-7)
    - Connecticut Commission on the Arts (Box 9-7)
    - Connecticut Conference of Mayors (Box 9-7)
    - Connecticut Conference of Municipalities (Box 9-7)
    - Connecticut Council on Soil & Water Conservation (Box 9-7)
    - Conn. Employees Union Indep. (Box 9-7)
    - Conn. Environmental Bulletin (Box 9-7)
    - CEPA (Box 9-7)
    - Connecticut Forest & Park Association (Box 9-7)
    - Conn. Horse Council (Box 9-7)
    - Connecticut Newsletter (Box 9-7)
    - Conn. River Watershed Council, Inc. (Box 9-7)
    - Conn. TB & Respiratory Disease Association (Box 9-7)
    - Conservation and Preservation, before 1976 (Box 9-7)
    - Conservation and Preservation, before 1977 (Box 9-7)
    - Conservation Directory (Box 9-7)
    - Contracts-Status Report (Box 9-7)
    - Corps of Engineers-Correspondence (Box 9-7)
    - Correspondence-Misc. (Box 9-7)
    - Council of Economic Advisors (Box 9-7)
    - CPEC (Box 9-7)
    - CREAC (Box 9-7)
    - Data Processing-Temp. Folder (Box 9-7)
    - Deferred Comp. Plan (Box 9-7)
    - Deferred Maintenance Project, 1973-1974 (Box 9-7)
    - DCA (Box 9-7)
    - DEPTAG (Box 9-7)
    - DeRosa, Joseph (Box 9-7)
    - Dues and Subscriptions (Box 9-7)
    - Eastman Trust (Box 9-7)
    - Economic Development Administration (Box 9-7)
    - Energy Research & Development (Box 9-7)
    - Environmental Education Act (Box 9-7)
    - Environmental Education (Box 9-7)
    - Environmental Impact Statements (Box 9-7)
    - Environmental Policy Act (Box 9-7)
    - Environmental Protection Act-P.A 872 (Box 9-7)
    - Environmental Protection Agencies (Box 9-7)
    - Environmental Protection Agencies, after 1973 (Box 9-7)
    - EPA, before 1974 (Box 9-2)
    - EPA Training Grant (Box 9-2)
    - Equipment Disposal Policy (Box 9-2)
    - Etherington Commission (Box 9-2)
    - Executive Committee Meeting (Box 9-2)
    - Executive Orders (Box 9-2)
    - Experiment in Management (Box 9-2)
    - Fairfield, town of (Box 9-2)
    - Farmland (Box 9-2)
    - Fair Labor Standards Act (Box 9-2)
    - Federal Funds-Forestry (Box 9-2)
    - Federal Funds-Water Pollution (Box 9-2)
    - Federal Receivable (Box 9-2)
    - Federal/State Relations (Box 9-2)
    - Federal/State Relations, before 1974 (Box 9-2)
    - Federal Time Records (Box 9-2)
    - Filer Committee-Structure of State Government (Box 9-2)
    - Finance Advisory Committee (Box 9-2)
    - Finance and Control-Correspondence (Box 9-2)
    - F&C Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 9-2)
    - F&C Correspondence, before 1974 (Box 9-2)
    - Financial Data-General (Box 9-2)
    - Financial Data Accounts (Box 9-2)
    - Financial Information, 1972 (Box 9-2)
    - Financial Projections-Fiscal, 1972 (Box 9-2)
    - Flow Chart (Box 9-2)
    - Forestry Audit (Box 9-2)
    - Forestry Info. (Box 9-2)
    - Freedom of Information Act (Box 9-2)
    - Fringe Benefits (Box 9-2)
    - General Electric (Box 9-3)
    - GE Solid Waste Contract (Box 9-3)
    - Gengras Committee on Productivity & Efficiency (Box 9-3)
    - Geological and Natural History Survey (Box 9-3)